Alright, this happened in middle school and still disgusts me to this day.
This may not be as crazy as the other stories on this subreddit but I need to share it.
So it was my first year of middle school and I had a friend who ill-called Jessica.
Jessica was in her last year when this story happened. So she had this crazy chemistry teacher
who was a big pervert however the school couldn't do anything as he didn't make sexual jokes to the
students or do anything he just had that vibe why no however this one day, one of his last days at
the school, he decided to follow Jessica into the girls bathroom and rape her there. Jessica was
silent for about days after that before she told the counselor of which he was arrested later that
day. And to top it off, Jessica was asexual and despised sex so it was even harder on her and
she ended up getting therapy that lasted until she was, let me repeat that she was in therapy
for years over one man. His sentence was years. This happened in, he was released last year.